question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "question": "The programming language &quot;Python&quot; is based off a modified version of &quot;JavaScript&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "Vehicles",
        "question": "The term &quot;GTO&quot; was originated by Ferrari?",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Animals",
        "question": "The Killer Whale is considered a type of dolphin.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Arcade Fire&#039;s &#039;The Suburbs&#039; won the Album of the Year award in the 2011 Grammys.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In the Disgaea series, any character can equip any weapon.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
